https://www.up-the-creek.com/privacy-and-cookies/

Privacy and CookiesWEBSITE VISITORSLike most website operators, up-the-creek.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. up-the-creek.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how up-the-creek.com’s visitors use its website. Up-the-creek.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Up-the-creek.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information.PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATIONUp-the-creek.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Up-the-creek.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.AGGREGATED STATISTICSUp-the-creek.com may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites.COOKIESA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Up-the-creek.com uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the website, and their website access preferences. Up-the-creek.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Up-the-creek.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Up-the-creek.com’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Up-the-creek.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Up-the-creek.com’s sole discretion. Up-the-creek.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Close this module
